<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>YJ Blog</title><link>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/</link><description>Recent content on YJ Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:56:20 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.younjinjeong.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dive deep to K-pop Singers #1</title><link>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/posts/k-pop/hahyunwoo/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2021 19:56:20 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/posts/k-pop/hahyunwoo/</guid><description>While I listen to my favorite Korean music today, I made up my mind to write a Korean pop post. Many famous k-pop stars and artists are out there, but I thought it would be good to introduce non-famous but great singers.
Today, the singer is HA Hyun Woo, who&amp;rsquo;s a frontman of Guckkasten band in Korea. In the band, his role is a leader, vocal, and guitar.
One of the greatest songs he sang, &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t Cry&amp;rdquo; in the show &amp;ldquo;King of Mask Singer&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Phrack magazine Vol7 Issue51 File Descriptor Hijacking</title><link>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/posts/translate/phrack-magazine/vol7-issue51-fd-hijacking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Mar 2021 16:21:21 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/posts/translate/phrack-magazine/vol7-issue51-fd-hijacking/</guid><description>블로그 테스트용으로 올려보는 예전 번역 10년전 KHDP에서 번역했었던
File descriptor hijacking 에 대한 글이 생각나
구글링을 해 보았더니, 수정없이 그냥들 보고 있는게 많더라.
사실, FD Hijacking 정도 볼 것 같으면
고딩의 저 어설픈 번역을 수정 할 법도 한데 그냥들 보고 있다는 말이지 홀홀..
10년이 지난 지금, 아직도 저런 공격방법이 통할 지는 모르겠지만
그 시절, 열정만을 가지고 밤새워 번역하고 코드 테스트도 해보며
이땅에 리눅스 및 BSD가 창궐하기전 홀로 즐겼던 세상으로 다시 돌아가 본다.</description></item><item><title>NAPI on Linux</title><link>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/posts/tech/napi/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 Mar 2021 01:37:04 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/posts/tech/napi/</guid><description>이제는 오래되어 버린 기술이지만, 2006년 경의 2.6.1x 대 커널에서의 NAPI 사용으로 인한 시스템 부하 절감 및 네트워킹 성능 향상은 경이로운 것이었다. 무지막지한 인터럽트 증가로 인하여 static 파일을 서비스 하는 웹 서버가 죽을똥 살똥 하던 모습이란.
언젠가 한번은 적어야지 했는데, 마치 Memory Hole 관련 문제처럼 언젠가는 잊어버리지 않을까 싶어, 생각 난 김에 포스팅 한다. 오랜만에 보는 HOW-To 문서를 번역할 예정이며, 요새 커널 버전과는 매우 동떨어져 있지만.. 뭐 그래도 잘 설명 되었으니까. 문서 원본은 아래의 링크에서 참조 할수있다.</description></item><item><title>About this Blog</title><link>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 23:59:02 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://blog.younjinjeong.io/about/</guid><description>This is a new version of &amp;ldquo;System Complete&amp;rdquo; blog.
System Compleat 블로그의 새로운 버전.
Distributed Computing, Cloud, and Open source.
이 블로그는 클라우드 및 분산 컴퓨팅, 그리고 오픈소스에 대한 주제를 주로 다룹니다.
About me Younjin Jeong Cloud Architect @DBS Bank ltd. South Korean in Singapore ex-Pivot, Principal Technologist ex-Amazonian, Solutions Architect RC, Cycle, Music, Driving Books Building Applications in the Cloud: Concpets, Patterns and Projects - Translate Cloud Native Java - Translate Netflix Cloud Engineering - Author SNS LinkedIn: https://www.</description></item></channel></rss>